that's played really well. Um, I can't
say enough about just the way that I
thought it was big to be able to get the
touchdown at the end of the half. It was
a great job by Matthew and the offense,
you know, and then to come out, there
was a little bit of a lull offensively
when we got the turnover, when we turn
the ball over and they have a chance to
really go up two possessions for our
defense to hold them to a field goal
right there and keep it at a onep
possession game. Unbelievable job. Uh,
unbelievable credit to our defense. Um,
and then offensively and being able to
go drive the length of the field to get
a touchdown. Some big time conversions.
I thought Matthew did a great job
keeping the ball in play. Devonte made
some plays. Obviously, Puka on the
fourth down to be able to score. Kairen
was tough as hell. You know, really the
offense in general. And then for the
defense to be able to get the stop, you
know, I mean, inverse when he forced the
fumble on the previous drive, but then
for the defense to be able to get the
stop right there, they punt it deep. And
then, you know, 22 Atwell is a guy, he's
been ready. He's had some opportunities
and he just delivered in a big time
moment to go for an 88 yard touchdown.
Cam Curl to be able to make the pick and
then offense to end with the ball. I I
love this team. Really proud of the way
that our field goal operation handled
themselves today against another really
good rush. Um I thought special teams
was really solid. This was a good team
win against a really good team. Um and
we won't have much time to enjoy it, but
uh it sure makes for a good next couple
days and we got to be ready to roll
against the Niners on Thursday.
>> Yeah, he got his uh he got his thumb
banged up a little bit. He came out and
uh looked pretty good in the second
half. What' you think? Think he was
okay? Yeah, he's going to be all right.
>> He's a stud. I mean, what a what a
tough, gritty I mean, there's so many
guys. I love this team. I just love the
way that they continue to just respond
to whatever is presented. Uh Puka
epitomizes that, but so do a lot of the
guys. Sarah,
>> what's it allow What's it about 2 that
lets him stay ready for a moment like
that? And what did it mean to you for
for him to be the one to deliver?
>> Well, I thought it was awesome. You
know, it got him in a man coverage right
there. He's running kind of a high angle
cut. You know, what a job by Matthew to
be able to find it, deliver a great
ball. 22 runs a great route and then
he's obviously got the gas to be able to
finish. So, can't say enough about him.
You just never know when your number's
going to be called. Um, and he's just
kind of stayed ready and that's a
tremendous credit to his mental
toughness, his resilience. I love him so
much. I'm really happy for him and u it
was a you know, we had to have that play
today. It was awesome.
>> How you assess Cam Curl as far as what
you this week in particular, but also
just in the game.
>> He's been a stud, Nick. I mean, the the
guy he's he's a grown man. um made play
after play and then obviously making the
pick to be able to uh you know get the
offense the ball back and and ultimately
close the game out. What a stud. Um so
glad to have him. I love Cam Curl.
>> Coach, when do you when do you know when
to dial that play 22? Is that more
situation?
>> You know what I mean honestly that
that's kind of an all-purpose play. That
was kind of an alert right there. And u
you know I I give Matthew a ton of
credit. You know Matthew and Tutu
deserve all the credit. That wasn't
anything about the play call. That was
about players bringing it to life. Um
and uh you know they sure delivered in a
big way right there.
>> What does that say about him? I mean
throughout his career
>> says a lot about
>> for opportunities and
>> it says a lot you know and I think uh
you know good things happen you know to
those who just stay consistent and and
stay ready. Um you know had some other
opportunities and and just ended up
delivering at the most critical moment.
Really happy for him. Like I said I love
I love the human being more importantly
and I was really happy for him to be
able to deliver and make a big play for
our team. Not surprised. Uh but it's a
tremendous credit to just his mindset,
his mental toughness, his resilience,
his ability to be ready when his number
was called.
>> When a draw, what do these dramatic
games finishes kind of help you grow as
a team bond?
>> Yeah, I think they do. You know, I
think, you know, some of the tougher
moments are where you really bond
together and where you really learn
about people. Uh but I think you can
sense that in the midst of games. You
know, you're going down, it seemed like
there was some momentum, but I never
felt anything but a steady no flinch
mentality from our group. That's how I
felt really through four games. Even
when Philly ended up mounting their
comeback, um, you know, we still gave
ourselves a chance at the end to be able
to do it. But, um, you know, we're on
to, uh, you know, this week. I'm really
proud of this group. And, man, it's
still so early in the season, but I
think we're being calloused and tested
in the right way. And most importantly,
we're coming together and, you know, we
got to continue to improve. But, uh, you
know, what a big opportunity that we
have on Thursday night with the Niners.
on the drive that you before the half,
you went down and scored and then when
you tied the game, those were drives
where everyone in the stadium knew you
guys had to throw the ball
>> and it and it worked. Why was that so
difficult the rest of the game?
>> Players executing. Well, I I wouldn't
say it was that like what do you mean by
that?
>> Well, I just mean the drive before the
half, everyone knew you're going to
throw. Yeah. You go down the field, you
score. You got to tie the game. Everyone
knows you're going to throw and you go
down.
>> I think our guys delivered. I think it
was really about execution. And
certainly there was uh you know some
other chances where I could have done a
better job of putting guys in the right
spots. But thought we handled the end of
the half situation the right way. That
touchdown to Devonte. The ball's got to
get into the end zone. What a big play
on the screen to Puka um on the second
down and 16 to get us a fresh set of
downs where we were able to clock it um
and then run that play that Devonte
ended up scoring on. Guys just delivered
and executed. And then you know the
other drive that you're talking about.
Um I just thought you know Matthew was
in total command. Um I thought our guys
protected well. It was able to regulate
a little bit of their rush because we
went fast and we kept the ball in play.
Kobe Parkinson makes a couple catches.
Puka see Devonte come to life and then
ultimately in the tight red area. Um to
be able to have that screen that ended
up being versus the zero blitz that got
us to a fourth down and two and then
Puka Nakua delivering in a big way. Uh
and then ultimately Cam getting the
turnover and then uh Tutu being able to
uh get the game winner. And I love the
fact that we finished with the ball.
Kairen had a couple tough runs. Um, you
know, to be able to allow us to take a
knee at the end right there. That's uh
that was a great team win for us.
>> Talk about Matthew being in total
control. Before the half, he takes him
96.
>> Yeah.
>> To tie it, he takes him the length of
the field. Do you sense that? Do you
feel that as you're calling the play?
>> Oh, yeah. I mean, and and really I
that's more of a question for him, but
you could feel he was in a rhythm and he
was seeing the field well. Thought we
protected really well. That allowed him
to be able to get through some
progressions, make some big time plays,
and he's a total stud. I love him.
>> Couple more guys.
>> What went into the decision to play
Peterson?
>> You know, Steve's still working himself
back. You know, I think Justin's played
really good football. You guys know how
much I love Steve and um you know, once
he gets back to full health, I look
forward to seeing, you know, what he's
able to do for us, but he was felt like
it was better to have him up in that
situation today. He's working, you know,
his tail off behind the scenes. And, you
know, Steve's going to be a big part of
what we're doing.
>> A lot of late quum in the beginning of
the game. He was really a workhorse for
you. Address that. Yeah, he did a great
job. You know, and then credit to them.
You know, they did some different things
to to slow us up. Uh being able to run
the football like Gerard said, I was
calling some bad plays, you know, in the
second half. And so, uh you know, I got
to be better right there.
>> What's happening with these two last
two?
>> Coach, last week you guys coraled Saquon
Barkley. This week, Jonathan Taylor, can
you just talk to me about the dominance
of the defensive line and when you're
big in a big moment when you need a big
play, Jared Verse coming?
>> Yeah, Jar Jared has been outstanding the
last couple weeks. He's a stud, you
know, and he just stays with it. Joe
Keniglio, Gif Smith, Drew Wilkins, you
know, really our guys. I can't say
enough about what a great job our group
has done. The players bring it to life.
I think they've got great coaches that
are helping them be able to bring it to
life. We've seen two of the best backs
and oh, by the way, here comes Christian
McCaffrey on Thursday. So, uh, you know,
there's no uh no rest for us, but love
where this group's at. Love the way that
they respond and I'm excited about the
challenge on Thursday.
>> Sean, emotions are such a big part of
every game. So when Mitchell gave up the
ball at the one inch line or whatever it
was, how does that affect the entire
team besides just the scoreboard?
>> Sometimes, you know, sometimes the
football gods are smiling down on you if
some things, you know, maybe haven't
gone your way um in the previous week.
So, uh we'll take it. That was a uh
don't ask me about that. Don't put a uh
don't put a cloud over an otherwise
sunny day right there.
is missing something.
>> Matthew, how would you describe that
touchdown pass that you
>> uh I mean it was a big one. Um obviously
a great route by uh by two. He um
slipped this guy out, made him fall
down. So um hell of a job finishing it
off. Uh not not number one in the
progression, that's for sure. But uh
just let you know you got to stay alive.
You know, whenever uh whenever your time
comes to make a play, he uh he obviously
made it for us. He's a huge play for us.
>> Talked about how despite only having one
catch this year, he's done what you guys
have asked him. Yeah.
>> And he's been there. What was it like
for you personally just to see him?
>> Oh man, I was so proud of him. So happy
for him. He's been practicing really
well. Um, you know, we dialed dialed it
up for him a couple times and it just
hasn't been the look um, you know, a few
times and like Sean said, I'll reiterate
it. He's done everything we've asked him
to do and and um, just so happy for him,
proud of him. Um, that's the guy he is.
Um, he just comes to work every day uh,
no matter what's going on around him.
Um, ready to work and and practice and
play and and made the biggest play and
the biggest moment today. So proud of
him, happy for him. Having the ability
to be able to spread the ball around
between Luca, him obviously Devonte. How
much does that really kind of ease the
load a little bit, especially going down
going down and knowing you have to make
those drives?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm just trying to throw
the ball where the coverage dictates.
Our guys do a hell of a job of winning
and uh you know, I'm I'm lucky to play
quarterback with this group of skilled
guys and really the guys up front. Um
it's it's a whole lot of fun. Um, you
know, there was some some lean moments
there in the third, early in the fourth.
Um, where, frankly, they did a nice job
of, you know, kind of affecting what we
were trying to do. Um, obviously got the
big turnover. What a job by our defense
right there, um, holding them to three.
Um, and, you know, then we were able to
kind of get going again. So, u, total
team effort today, but it definitely,
uh, it's definitely nice. You know, we
got guys that can win at all levels of
the defense and make plays after the
catch, which is awesome.
When you guys were down a touchdown and
you needed to score, you went down and
scored. When it's
>> first down right before half on a four
yard line, you go right down and score.
Yep.
>> What is it about you? What is it about
your body that you just seem more I
don't know if it's accurate or not, seem
more calm.
>> Yeah. Um, you know, there were a couple
instances today where we were able to
jump the ball, play with some tempo, and
um, I thought Sean did a hell of a job
mixing and matching those times, calling
it, um, you know, kind of through
through the pass game there late in the
game. And, um, you know, when somebody
does that, uh, shoot, man, makes me want
to deliver for him. And, um, so, uh,
don't care where we start, you know,
it's all about finishing in the right
spot. So, we did a nice job of, you
know, getting three three long touchdown
drives. Um, you know, throwing the
football the majority of the time, doing
a nice job, playing with some tempo. So,
we've always mixed and matched that, you
know, as as uh as I've been here, um you
know, different it iterations of it a
little bit, but uh it was big for us
today. There's no question about that.
>> And when you see your defense hold at
that very end, are you jogging on the
field thinking
>> I'm sure you're not thinking, oh, 80
yard touchdown to two. Yeah. What are
you thinking?
>> Oh, just go get go win a game. You I
mean, go win a game. Um they did their
job. They did a hell of a job really all
day. Um, I didn't think it was going to
be a one player, but uh, that was the
look. Uh, it was kind of like the last
thought in my head jogging out on the
field when we called the play. But, um,
everybody's got to be alive and and Tutu
did a hell of a job winning his route
and then finishing the thing off. So,
uh, big play and then shoot, what does
our defense do? Go out there, get a
turnover again, and then I thought our
guys up front, we get we call two runs.
We don't have to punt it back. No weird
stuff at the end of the game. Just two
runs, take a knee, get out of there. So,
uh, that's a good job of finishing the
game.
>> Yeah, I mean, uh, you know, it's a quick
turnaround for us. We're playing again
on Thursday in a few days. So, um, sure,
uh, sure nice to come away with this one
in a win. It's a really good football
team. We just played physical on both
sides of the line of scrimmage. Um, you
know, you look at their skill position
guys who they got at running back and
receiver. Daniel's playing great and
tight end. So, um, big challenge for our
defense. I thought they played great.
And then um you know we we struggled
there a little bit um but found some uh
found some good momentum late and were
able to win it. So uh definitely nice
when you got a quick game um turnaround
so we'll take it.
>> After that throw the two running down
the field arms outstretched.
>> Yeah.
>> What's going through your mind in that?
>> I'm saying wild stuff. I was actually
miked up today and I was coming off the
field. I'm like hey man we're going to
have to
we're going to have to do some heavy
editing. It'll probably just be a lot of
silence. Um but uh I don't even know. I
just go crazy. Um I just so excited for
our team, so excited for that moment. Um
it's what you play for. So, uh I'll see
I'll save the expletives for you. But it
was uh it was fun.
>> Sean keeps using the word gritty for
this team. Would you agree?
>> Oh, 100%. Um you know, it's that's what
it's all about. I mean, it's the NFL.
It's never just these show up, you know,
kick ass for four quarters and go home.
I mean, it's just we're playing good
football teams. playing a 3 and0 Colts
team today that um you know is arguably
the hottest team in the NFL coming in
here. So punted like one time or
something, I don't know. So um knew it
was going to be a dog fight and uh just
proud of our guys. Uh it's something
that when I wasn't practicing in
training camp, I could see it from afar
and I was excited and proud, you know,
to be associated with those guys and
then uh you know, getting to be able to
get back into it and play and and lead
these guys. It's uh it's a whole lot of
fun to be a part I mean, I just feel
like I'm a part of a great group of guys
that all trying to do everything they
can to win games and pull for each
other, which is cool.
>> How difficult it really is to play two
games in four days.
>> Yeah, it's tough. It's it gets tougher
and tougher for me every year, but uh
we'll do a great job of turning our
turning the bodies over. Um you know, I
guess maybe the one um you know,
positive for us is we're in division, so
we kind of know a decent amount of these
guys, right? And what they're kind of
about. Um, so it's not, you know, some
opponent we rarely ever play or ever see
and you got to really deep dive and
learn, you know, everything there is to
learn. So, um, that part of it is good.
Um, but yeah, I mean, I just think
Thursday practice when I jog out on the
field, like sometimes how you feel going
out to that and you're like going to
have to do that for game day, but
adrenaline is a hell of a thing. So,
we'll be all right.
>> Last one. I feel like every week we ask
you about a a big Pa game, but just what
is the luxury like to have as as
receivers steady as he is? And how does
what he's doing kind of help out some of
those other receivers in there?
>> Yeah, I mean he's he's uh he's as tough
as they come. Um you know, he did a hell
of a job again today. We called his
number quite a few times. The fourth
down was huge. Um the touchdown catch.
Um you know, he just uh he's he's a heck
of a football player. We're lucky to
have him on our team. I think his uh
play style rubs off on everybody on our
team, not just offense. You know, I
think our defense looks at him like,
"Shit, we'll ride with that guy all
day." And and I know that's how we feel
on offense. So, he made some great plays
today. Made a great catch on an incut,
sliding in there. Um you know, he just
he did what he always does. Made some
great tough plays and and um we're happy
to have him in that room.
>> Cool.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Well, we go and check that.